你是"做"了什么让人家给你20块小费
Who or what did you do to get this $20 tip?
我昨晚推一位坐轮椅的顾客回家
Because I wheeled a customer home the other night,
才拿到5块小费
and all I got was a 5.
而且我跟他亲热完 还帮他洗了个澡
And that was after we made out and I gave him a bath.
刚才那桌女士问我们这有什么特别的
The lady at that table asked me what was special here,
我回答"我曾是特别的姑娘" 然后就喷泪
and I said, "I used to be," and then I burst into tears.
我缺钱做指甲时都会用这招
I pull that out whenever I need a manicure.
又到了每年的这个时候啦
Well, it's that time of year again.
真是羡慕嫉妒恨
I'm so jealous.
你的大姨妈居然一年只来一次
I can't believe you only get your period once a year.
是纳税季节啦 而我的会计说
It's tax season, and my accountant said
我有退税款能拿呢
I'm getting a refund.
他还赞美了我的莫卡辛[鹿皮鞋]呢
He also complimented these moccasins,
而在这里只会被你们耻笑
which are also controversial around here.
因为那鞋子都叫做"莫"
Well, they do have the word "mock..."
-"傻" -"逼"了
- "ass..." - " And "Sin."
这也是为什么我从来不穿全身服
This is why I never wear overalls,
因为你们俩会...
'cause you two would be...
-全身... -想吐吗
- Over.. - disgusted?
正是如此
Precisely.
厄尔 看到你我想起来
Oh, Earl, that reminds me.
我忘了给你 拿去
I forgot. Here you go.
我帮你报完税了
I finished your taxes.
以后你不可以再把你的
And for the future you cannot claim
大麻药头列为"抚养亲属"[依赖]了
your weed dealer as a dependent.
为什么不行 我很依赖大麻啊
I don't know why. I'm very dependent on weed.
麦克斯 我最近都有在帮忙大家报税
Max, since I've been helping everyone with their taxes,
主要是因为除了报税 我的金融学位就只剩
mostly because the only other time I get to use my financial degree
数家里剩多少棉花棒时能用上
is counting how many q-tips we have left,
剩5根
Five--
是三根 我掉了两根进马桶
Three. I dropped two in the toilet,
蟑螂兄拿去当他小船的船桨了
and the cockroach is using them as oars for his boat.
画面一定很可爱
Ha. That'll be cute.
有两件事我是不会跟你谈的
Look, there are two things I won't talk about--
我的税务和你的飞行梦想
Taxes or your flying dreams.
别傻了 卡洛琳 你哪都去不了
Face it, Caroline. You're not going anywhere.
那我们也得谈谈我们小店的税务
Okay, well, we have to talk about our taxes
以及我们要索回哪些税款
and what we're gonna claim,
还有 你不能表示[索款]我毁了你人生
and, no, you cannot claim I'm ruining your life.
为啥 我去年这么做还拿回了10块钱呢
Why? I did that last year and got $10 back.
半夜2点 关门时间到 走吧
2:00 A.M., closing time. Let's go.
才12点半好吗
It's only 12:30.
-麦克斯 想得真美 -别这样 早点走嘛
- Nice try, Max. - Come on, let's leave early.
我比我的胸罩还累
I'm more exhausted than my bra.
太好了 你们还没关门
Whoa, good, you're still open.
我的未婚妻想吃小蛋糕
My fiancee wants a cupcake,
她心一想 事就得成
and she always gets what she wants.
你们好
Hi.
我也很想要在度假胜地有小别墅
I mean, I really want a house in the Hamptons,
但是来一个小蛋糕也行啦
but I'll take a cupcake.
我其实不是我话中的那种人
I'm nothing like that sounded.
不用道歉
Don't apologize.
我完全就是你话中的那种人
I'm everything like that sounded.
宝贝 我马上回来
Oh, I'll be right back, babe.
有个流浪汉正用购物袋在我的保时捷上
There's a homeless guy building a shopping bag house
盖他的窝呢
around the porsche.
可惜了 流浪汉差点就有前保时捷[阳台]了
Too bad. That homeless guy almost had a front porsche.
他很讨厌这一带
He hates this neighborhood.
他也不过就是被人拿枪威胁过一两回嘛
So you've been held up at gunpoint one or two times?
带种一点 你们说是吧
It's like, grow a pair, right?
你想要吃什么口味呢
So what are you eating?
巧克力味吧
Um, chocolate.
等等 我想还是红丝绒吧
But, wait, now I'm thinking red velvet.
蒂姆求婚的时候把戒指放红丝绒里了
Tim put my ring in one when he proposed.
他用我们的小蛋糕求婚的吗
Oh, he proposed with one of our cupcakes?
真是太浪漫了
That's so sweet.
是啊
Yeah, it was.
如果我没把戒指吞下去 一切都很完美
I mean, it was like a whole thing because I swallowed it,
但在"屎落戒出"之后
but, once it passed,
戒指的确很美
really so pretty.
我给了20块让他移去迷你库柏边
I gave him a 20 to move to that Mini Cooper
别在我们车边筑巢了
instead of our car.
记得提醒我下次叫阿憨"迷你库柏"
Remind me to start calling Han "Mini Cooper."
宝贝 我在想...
Babe, I've been thinking.
惨了 这下不妙了
Uh-oh. That's never good.
宝贝 很妙的 听我说
No, it's great, babe. Listen.
既然你是用她们的小蛋糕跟我求婚的
So, since you proposed to me with one of their cupcakes,
我在想 那就让她们包办结婚蛋糕吧
I was thinking that these girls should do our wedding cake.
但宝贝 我们已经订了结婚蛋糕了
But, babe, we already ordered a wedding cake.
一千三呢 还记得吗 宝贝
$1,300. Remember, babe?
我知道 可是宝贝
I know, but, babe.
电影《小猪宝贝》里都没说这么多次"宝贝"
They said babe less in the movie Babe.
你们这里承办婚礼蛋糕吗
So do you guys do wedding cakes?
-不做 -做
- No. - Yes.
我不会做 她会做
I don't. She does.
她才是烘焙师
She's the baker, and, yes,
而我们这里也常承办结婚蛋糕
we do tons of wedding cakes.
同性恋结婚蛋糕 异性恋结婚蛋糕
Gay weddings, straight weddings.
尿床[结婚]
Bed wettings.
克雷儿 你怎么高兴怎么来
Claire, you do whatever you want,
但我要先上车等了
but I'm gonna wait in the car.
我承受不了再搞一次蛋糕的事 宝贝
I just can't do the cake stuff again, babe.
他不想搞蛋糕的事
He doesn't want to do the cake stuff.
我还不想"搞屁眼"的事呢
Well, I don't want to do the butt stuff.
你懂我意思吧
You know what I mean?
-不懂 -懂
- No. - Yes.
要不你进来我们里面慢慢谈吧
Why don't you come in and we can talk about it?
-从旁边餐厅进来 -好
- Enter through the diner. - Okay.
等会见
See you guys in a sec.
你脑子有病啊
What is wrong with you?
我不是说过店里不许再有更多白人蠢妞了吗
I told you I didn't want any more white girls in the shop.
而且我们什么时候开始做结婚蛋糕了
And since when do we do wedding cakes?
从她男人说一千三的时候
Since that guy said $1,300.
麦克斯 你能行 你都上过烘焙学校了
You can do this, Max. You went to pastry school.
我也去上过高中啊
I also went to high school,
但我也不知道洛克·哈德森演的是哪个总统
but I can't tell you which president Rock Hudson was.
我不做结婚蛋糕
I don't do wedding cakes.
好啦 我知道由于你最近刚分手
Okay, I know this may not be the best time for you
所以让你做第一个结婚蛋糕 有点不合时宜
to make your first wedding cake because of your recent breakup.
跟迪克无关好吗
Oh, it's not about Deke.
你忘了扫爆炸头男出门的正是小女子了吗
If you remember, I'm the one who sent his 'fro out the door.
婚礼蠢爆了
Weddings are just stupid.
这件庆祝爱情的蠢事
This whole idea of celebrating love?
拜托 爱情比克里斯·克里斯帝还狗屁不通
I mean, love works out less than Chris Christie.
走过这扇门
Right through here.
小姐 就是这里啦
There you go, miss.
谢谢
Thanks.
你还有事吗
Did you want something else?
能有什么我全要了
I'll take whatever I can get.
好了 没你的事了
Okay, we're done.
你很幸运了 今天早上
You're lucky. This morning, a cannoli shell
一个奶油甜馅煎饼卷告他性骚扰呢
pressed sexual harassment charges against him.
天啊 两位
Oh, my God, you guys.
你们的店超口爱啊
Your shop is so adorbs.
对了 我叫克雷儿
I'm Claire, by the way.
我在贝德福德大道有家店
I owned a store on Bedford Ave.
是一家女装店 叫"女装逼就滚"
A dress shop called "Get the frock out."
我记得那家店
Oh, I remember that place.
是不是就在一家叫
Wasn't it right next to the hair salon,
"编发不思议"的美发店旁
"Unbeweavable"
是啊 就在"编发不思议"
Yeah, yeah, between "Unbeweavable"
跟一家犹太净食的奶昔店中间
and the kosher smoothie place
奶昔店是叫"流浪犹太汁"
called "The wandering juice."
我很喜欢他们的犹太烛台橙汁
I love their menorah-nge juice.
我一直梦想着有天开家女装店
Yeah, you know, it was always my dream to have a dress shop.
但开了一年 生意一直很差
But then after a year hardly anyone was coming in,
然后我就想 也许该"滚"的人是我
and I was like, maybe I should get the frock out.
-所以我放弃了 -我完全懂
- So I bailed. - I totally get it.
我们第一间店也倒了 但我们爬起来
Our first shop failed, but we got up,
拍掉身上的灰
dusted ourselves off--
麦克斯则是连续四天喝得醉醺醺
Well, Max went on a four-day bender,
但我还是找到了她 替她拍拍灰
but I found her and dusted her off,
然后我们东山再起
Then we started again.
多亏你去下载了"寻找醉酒室友"手机软件
Yeah, good thing you downloaded the "Find your drunk roommate" App.
所以你们虽然失败了 却还是没放弃吗
Oh, so you guys kept going, even though you failed?
为啥 你们没有男朋友吗
Why? Don't you have boyfriends?
所以你们什么哪天结婚
So when are you two getting married?
三天后
Oh, in three days.
三天后 你好淡定啊
Three days? You're so calm.
09年 客机迫降哈德逊河 我就在机上
Yeah, well, I was in the plane that crashed in the hudson,
在那次事情后 我什么都不怕不怕啦
so after that everything's just kind of been "meh."
所以你知道要哪种蛋糕了吗
So do you know what kind of cake you want?
当然 要传统一点
Absolutely. Something traditional,
比较老派一点 就是比较浪漫
something very old school, you know, very romantic,
等等 现在我在想
But, wait, now I'm thinking
你们俩都这么酷
You guys are so cool,
要不我们做有威廉斯堡嬉皮士风的怪蛋糕
what if we did something with a weird hipster Williamsburg vibe?
所以你要个坐拥信托基金
So you want an obnoxious cake on a trust fund
穿着嘲讽T恤 讨人厌到爆的蛋糕吗
wearing an ironic t-shirt with HPV?
等等 我现在又在想柔和的春天风
But, wait, now I'm thinking pastels for spring.
再等等 我现在又在想
Oh, but, wait, now I'm thinking,
色彩缤纷 我喜欢小丑
colors. I love clowns.
她改变想法的次数比我换内衣裤还多
Wow, she changes her mind more than I change my underwear.
所以就两次吗
So twice?
苏菲 在你的报税单上
Sophie, on your tax form here,
你写了你的职业是"苏菲"
you listed your occupation as "Sophie."
是啊 这可是个全职工作 宝贝
Yeah, it's a full-time job, baby.
还有 谁会要退五千块钱的睫毛膏税金啊
And who claims $5,000 worth of mascara?
这是我清洁生意的公司营运费用
It's a business deduction for my cleaning business.
那是我给我的波兰未成年女工的奖励
I give it out to all the underage girls from Poland as treats.
虽然她们手边刷着马桶
Just because you're scrubbing toilets
但不代表她们的眼睛就不能美啊
doesn't mean your eyes can't pop.
你有任何正当的东西
Do you have any legitimate anything
是可拿来用在任何事上的吗
that we can use for anything?
这有张数目大的发票
Here's a big receipt.
两千五的伏特加
$2,500 for stolichnaya.
酒品不能抵税
You can't write off liquor.
是伊莲娜·芙特佳啦
No, Irina Stolichnaya.
她是帮我修眉毛的
Yeah, she waxes my eyebrows.
以及我"下面的眉毛"
And my downstairs eyebrows.
这表格上没有地方是给
Okay, well, there's no line on this form
"下面的眉毛"的
for downstairs eyebrows,
所以我就写入家庭办公室吧
so I'm just gonna list it as home office.
我的确是靠"它"办了不少公
Yeah, well, I do work out of it.
卡洛琳 麦克斯呢
Caroline, where's Max?
虽然我很享受两个小时
As much as I enjoy a two-hour break
不用被叫为"小女人"的时光
from being called a tiny woman,
但她不能不干活啊
She's supposed to be working.
麦克斯 蛋糕如何了
Max, how's the cake going?
那新娘就是个疯婆子
That bride's a mess.
她在改变主意的过程中又改变了主意
She changed her mind while she was changing her mind.
别用上层柜子的好货啊
Not the good stuff on the top shelf!
反正你平常也拿不到 迷你库柏
Oh, you can't reach it anyway, Mini Cooper.
她傻逼了吧 哥有折叠梯
Joke's on her. I have a collapsible ladder.
你好 克雷儿 麦克斯正在做呢
Oh, hi, Claire. Max is working on it right now.
你又有在想吗
Oh, you've been thinking?
卡洛琳 卫生巾钱能抵税吗
Caroline, can I get anything for a panty liner?
我正在跟克雷儿[清楚]通电话
I'm on the phone with Claire.
你是说脑子不清楚那位吗
You mean un-Claire?
她想要做几个改变
She wants to make a couple changes.
-我该怎么回她 -告诉她我恨她
- What should I tell her? - Tell her I hate her.
不用 这样吧 我来告诉她
No, you know what, I'll tell her.
我喜欢告诉别人事情 电话给我
I love to tell people things. Give me the phone.
麦克斯 我求你了 一千三呢
Max, I beg you. $1,300.
天啊 她太神经病了
Oh, my God. She is so crazy.
我应该直接做个超大的蛋糕
I should just make a giant cake
让一个精神科医生从里面跳出来
and have a psychiatrist pop out of it.
电话给我
Give me the phone.
克雷儿宝贝 怎么啦 宝贝
Hey, Claire, babe. What's happening, babe?
麦克斯 我在想
Max, I've been thinking,
我知道我说过不要翻糖糖霜
And I know I said I didn't want the fondant frosting,
但是我刚才看到另一个结婚蛋糕的图
but now I just saw a photo of another wedding cake
翻糖蛋糕美翻了
that was so gorge.
所以我就在想...
And I started thinking...
行 没问题
Uh-huh. Sure. No problem.
所以我们可以做翻糖吗
So then we can do the fondant?
当然 绝对翻糖
Yes, definitely fondant.
太好了 再见 爱你哟
Perfect. Bye. Love you.
我也爱你
Love you too.
麦克斯 我知道你费了很多功夫
Max, I know you worked hard,
也知道你心里听到要修改会很不爽
and you're probably upset about having to change it.
我感觉到了浓厚的杀气
I'm sensing a lot of hostility
而这杀气跟那对新人无关
that has nothing to do with that couple
反而是跟你与某位
and may be more about you
有缘无分的新郎比较有关
and a certain groom that didn't happen.
什么 难道把一对新人的头烧了
What, you can't light a couple's head on fire
就一定得是跟前男友有关吗
without it being about your ex-boyfriend?
麦克斯 我知道你很伤心
Max, I know you're sad about it.
我昨晚都听到你哭了
I heard you crying last night.
哭的人是你
That was you crying.
好吧 反正某人哭了
Well, someone was crying.
天啊 麦克斯 太漂亮了
Oh, my God. Max. It's beautiful.
你做得真是太出色了
You did an amazing job.
这蛋糕真是赞赞赞
That's quite a cake cake cake.
淡定 我不过是做了个蛋糕 又不是折好床单
Calm down. I made a cake. I didn't fold a fitted sheet.
我喜欢这对新的新郎和新娘
Ooh, and I like the new bride and groom.
对了 我把垃圾堆那那对拿出来了
By the way, I fished the other ones out of the garbage
以防下次会接到烧伤患者婚礼的订单
in case we ever get a burn victim wedding.
我把备用的糖霜拿上了 走吧
Okay, I got the extra icing. Let's go.
我们要用双手抓着
Now grab it with two hands
然后用膝盖顶起来
and lift with your knees.
你觉得应该这么弄过去吗
Oh, is that how you think it should go?
我本来还打算一头栽进去
'cause I was gonna grab it with my head
用我的脸顶着走呢
and lift it with my face.
搞定 搞定 搞定
Got it. Got it. Got it.
等一下
Ooh. Oh, wait.
搞定 搞定 搞定
Got it. Got it. Got it.
-地上有油 -搞定
- Grease puddle. - Got it.
搞定 搞定
Got it. Got it.
-蟑螂 -搞定
- Roach. - Got it.
贝德福德大道
Bedford avenue.
搞定 搞定 搞定
Got it. Got it. Got it.
搞定 搞定
Got it. Got it.
注意开关门
Watch the doors.
-麦克斯 这太[沉]重了 -我知道
- Max, this is so heavy. - I know.
我们俩成年人 居然打不起车
We're two grown women who can't afford a taxi.
那边有个座 我们可以把蛋糕放下了
Oh, there's a seat over there. We can put this down.
搞定 搞定 搞定
Got it. Got it. Got it.
我怪科学
I blame science.
没事干嘛让人活这么久
People shouldn't be living this long.
-麦克斯 我需要休息 -我也是
- Max, I need a break. - Me too.
或许休息个两周
Maybe just like two weeks apart.
没电话 没你 与世隔绝
Like, no phone calls, nothing.
我是说抬不动蛋糕啦
I mean the cake.
而且你是爱我的
And you love me.
去那边吧 那边人少
Other side. Less crowded.
这家伙看不见 真倒霉
Oh, this guy can't see. Just our luck.
往左走 先生
To the left, sir.
是你的左边啦
Other left!
搞毛啊 现在流行瞎子吗
Oh, what, is everybody blind now?
你们跳舞给谁看啊
who are you even dancing for?
整个车厢都是瞎子
Everyone's blind.
搞定 搞定 搞定
Got it. Got it. Got it.
没力了 没力了
Losing it. Losing it.
坚持住 坚持住 没力了
Holding it. Holding it. Losing it.
恢复元气 搞定 搞定
Second wind. Got it. Got it.
第一大道 第一大道站到了
First Avenue. First Avenue station.
那边那边 快放下来
There, there. Put it down.
麦克斯 我们应该是搞定了
Max, I think we got it.
完全没搞定
Don't got it.
搞定 搞定 搞定 搞定
Got it. Got it. Got it. Got it.
搞定了
Got it.
这蛋糕看起来完美无缺 谁都看不出来
This cake looks perfect. You would never know.
所以我才喜欢用翻糖 它能遮盖一切
That's why I'm fond of the fondant. Covers everything.
等他们意识到这蛋糕是一半蛋糕
We'll be long gone by the time they realize
一半无线电器材公司的泡沫塑料时 我们早走了
it's half cake-half styrofoam from the Radio Shack garbage.
你们好 我是这场婚礼兼自己葬礼的策划人
Hi. I'm the wedding planner/ my own funeral planner
因为我快要被这场婚礼搞死了
'cause it ain't going great.
你们是蛋糕妹吗
You the cake girls?
你觉得因为我们俩都是女的
You think just 'cause we're two girls
而且还站在一个大蛋糕旁边 就是蛋糕妹了吗
with a giant cake we're the cake girls?
你觉得因为我在假笑
You think 'cause I'm fake smiling
我就不会把你们踢飞出去了吗
I won't throw you down a flight of stairs?
你会这么做吗 麻烦给我你的名片
You do that? Do you have a card?
抱歉 我们早上历尽千辛万苦才把蛋糕弄来这里
Sorry. We had a rough morning getting this here.
就你们辛苦吗 她又把菜单改了
You? She changed the menu again.
我为了那个疯婆子 花了一个早上的时间
I spent the whole morning making 17 turkeys look
想办法让17只火鸡看起来像17只火腿
like 17 hams for that crazy bitch.
拜托 这么说有点过吧
Oh, come on, that's a little har--
什么 她不愿意出房门
What? She won't come out of her room?
新娘临阵退缩了
The bride has cold feet.
那个疯婆子
That crazy bitch.
我有个疯狂的主意
Here's a crazy idea.
不如先把蛋糕钱付了
How about the check for the cake?
我把之前跟"自己做冰棒"那家伙说的话
All right, I'm gonna tell you two what I told
再跟你们复述一遍
the make-your-own-popsicle guy.
新娘没走上红毯前 谁也拿不到一分钱
Nobody gets paid until the bride walks down the aisle.
谁都别想
Nobody.
婚礼上会有冰棒吗
There's gonna be popsicles?
看来她没那么疯嘛
She's not that crazy.
我们现在该怎么办
So what are we gonna do now?
-走吧 -麦克斯 我们不能走
- Let's go. - Max, we can't go.
我们需要这笔钱
We need this money.
我们还需要一个不会传染皮疹的浴帘
We also need a shower curtain that doesn't give us rashes.
等一下 我们真的很需要这笔钱
But, wait, we really need this cake money.
我们也真的很需要一个
We also really need a toilet
冲一次就能冲干净的马桶
that flushes everything the first time.
你在做蛋糕的时候 我在算我们的纳税额
While you were doing the cake, I was doing our taxes.
我们欠山姆大叔[美国政府]一千五
And we owe Uncle Sam $1,500.
靠 为啥我认识的每个大叔都想"搞"死我
Man, why does every Uncle I know try to screw me?
所以我们该怎么办
So what are we gonna do?
你也听到那女人怎么说了
You heard that woman--
新娘没走上红毯前 谁也拿不到一分钱
nobody gets paid until the bride walks down the aisle.
包括我们自己
Nobody.
我们进来啦 原来明艳照人的新娘在这里
Knock-knock. There's the gorgeous bride.
你的婚纱真美
Your dress is beautiful.
穿着这么美的婚纱就应该
It's a beautiful dress to get married in
立刻去隔壁房间结婚
right now in the next room.
我不喜欢 我要脱掉
No, I hate it. I'm taking it off.
我不会穿这套婚纱
I'm not wearing this dress
更不会穿那套 或是那套
or that one or that one.
因为我在想 婚姻是愚蠢的
Because I'm thinking marriage is stupid.
-太愚蠢了 -麦克斯
- So stupid. - Max .
既愚蠢又美丽 人人都应该这样做
Stupid beautiful, and everyone should do it.
不 不适合我
Nope. It's not for me.
就像内裤
Like underwear.
你会没事的
Oh, you'll feel fine
只要你穿回这套婚纱
as soon as you get back in this dress.
或是穿上那套 或那套
Or that dress or that dress.
我感觉你们在逼我穿上婚纱
Okay, I feel like you guys are forcing me into this dress.
才没有
That's ridiculous.
我们怎么可能为了钱逼你穿婚纱
Forcing you into a dress for money?
那该死的头纱呢
Now where's that freaking veil?
不是这个
Nope, not that one.
这是备用头纱
This was just a backup veil.
会完全挡住我的脸
You can't even see my face.
是以防我长疱疹准备的
It was in case I got herpes.
你们也知道长疱疹有多可怕
You know how it is.
-我知道 -不知道
- Yeah. - No.
-总而言之 我在想... -想什么
- Anyways, I'm thinking... - What,
七件能导致我们一分钱都拿不到的事情吗
like seven different things all resulting in us not getting paid?
听着 我在想
Listen, I'm thinking
或许我太早放弃了我的服装店
that maybe I bailed out of my shop too soon.
我才开了一年就不干了
I mean, I left after only a year.
难道就因为害怕吗
Why? 'cause I was just scared?
人人都会害怕失败
Well, everybody's afraid of failure.
不 不是失败
No, not failure.
有一群黑帮在我服装店门口枪战
There was a gang shooting in front of my dress shop.
害我不得不埋了两个家人模特
I had to bury two mannequins.
给你个建议供以后参考 在脸上画颗泪珠
For future reference, just draw a teardrop on your face,
他们就会把战场挪到香蕉共和国
and they'll move it to Banana Republic.
我是说 对你们来说开店也不容易
Well, I mean, it wasn't easy for you guys, right?
但你们没有放弃
But you hung in there,
所以现在才拥有一个成功的大蛋糕店
and now you have this big, successful cake business.
-我们撒谎了 -生意很糟糕
- We lied. - It's terrible.
-我们是废柴 -快去结婚吧
- We're losers. - Get married.
克雷儿 唯一比开店还难的就是
Claire, the only thing harder than building a business
寻找真爱
is finding love.
你看她 刚刚跟心爱的人分手
Look at her. She just lost someone she loves,
老实说连她自己都觉得
and quite frankly she doesn't think
这辈子不会再遇见这么合适的人了
it's ever gonna happen for her again.
其实我们大伙都这么想
I mean, none of us do.
连阿憨也是吗
Not even Han?
是啊 就是他开始提起这事的
No, he's the one who brought it up.
克雷儿 有谁比我们更了解你呢
Claire, who knows you better than us?
你得结婚
You're getting married.
你说得对 我是该结婚
You're right. I should get married.
-但不是嫁给蒂姆 -什么
- But not to Tim. - What?
你们会帮我转告他的 对吗
You guys will tell him for me, right?
告诉他我配不上他 是我对不起他
Tell him I'm no good. Tell him I'm sorry.
算了 你们想怎么说就怎么说
You know what, tell him whatever you want.
你们决定好了 我很随和的
You guys decide. I'm easy.
她随和个屁 最难搞就是她
You know what she's not? Easy.
你也听到那女人怎么说了
You heard that woman--
新娘没走上红毯前 谁也拿不到一分钱
nobody gets paid until the bride walks down the aisle.
在策划人把支票给我前
Now, remember, don't lift this veil
记得千万不要把头纱撩起来
until the party planner hands me that check.
为什么不是你穿婚纱
Why don't you have to wear the dress?
你基本上就是个适合嫁人的纯洁处女
You're practically a virgin.
麦克斯 必须有人穿婚纱走红毯 而我不行
Max, somebody has to walk down the aisle, and I can't do it.
婚姻对我是有意义的
Marriage means something to me,
而且我这辈子只打算走一次红毯[过道]
and I only plan to walk down that aisle once.
你在药店卖宫颈感染药的过道也这么说过
You also said that about the yeast infection aisle at CVS,
但上周六你又去了
but there you were last Saturday
还假装是买儿童止咳糖浆
pretending to buy children's cough syrup.
走吧
Let's go.
等等我 麦克斯
Wait, Max.
麦克斯 等等
Max, wait, wait!
等等我 麦克斯
Wait, Max!!
走红毯时要像今天就是你的大日子一样
Now just walk down the aisle like it's your special day.
退下 新娘才不会跟蛋糕妹说话
Go. The bride never talks to the cake lady.
人们会问"那是谁呀"
People are like, "Who's that?"
如果你觉得他们现在在想"那是谁"
If you think they're like, "who's that?" now,
等会你头纱掀起时 他们会更有那感觉的
wait a few minutes till that veil gets lifted.
难以置信 她居然真的走上红毯了
Can't believe it. She's actually walking down that aisle.
是呀 走红毯那个绝对是她
Yup, that's totally her walking down the aisle.
所以你现在可以把支票给我了
So the check, you can hand it to me now.
你真美 宝贝
You look stunning, babe.
快点 快点
Come on, come on, come on.
直接给我最上面那张就行了
I'll just take whatever check's on top.
宝贝 宝贝 慢着
Babe, babe, wait.
现在我想结婚了
Now I'm thinking I do want to get married.
宝贝 如果你在那 那这是谁
Babe, if you're there, who is...
你好呀
'Sup?
宝贝 之前我说不想要小孩
Babe, I know I said I didn't want any kids,
但现在我想要四个
but now I'm thinking four.
宝贝 这话你应该在我结扎之前说的
Babe, you should have said that before the vasectomy.
你可以解除的嘛
You can always reverse it.
你不早说
Again.
你是新人的父亲吗
So you're the father, huh?
而你居然没抛妻弃子
And you stuck around.
你这么做也挺有意思的
That's an interesting way to play it.
我拿到支票了 我们可以走了
Okay, I got the check. We can leave.
现在不行 我们在跳父女舞呢
Not now. I'm doing the father-daughter dance.
介意换人吗
May I cut in?
我是要跟她跳
Oh, no, with her.
如果你想泡我
If you're trying to hook up with me,
那抱歉你来晚了
you're a little late.
那位爸爸刚把房间钥匙偷塞给我了
That dad just slipped me his room key.
你当新娘的样子真可爱
You really do make a lovely bride.
多谢 你知道我把
Oh, thanks. You know I have one
一只火腿火鸡塞到我内裤里了 对吧
Of those ham turkeys in my underwear, right?
我还以为你的爽样是因为看到我呢
Oh, I thought you were just happy to see me.
这感觉真好
This is nice.
那个蛋糕真的很漂亮
And that cake really is beautiful.
谢谢
Thanks.
真希望可以给...
Wish I could have showed it to...
迪克看
Deke.
是啊
Yeah.
你真的没事吗
So are you really okay?
我知道你很爱他
I know you loved him.
我是爱他 这样才惨
I did, which is the worst
因为会让我感觉更像个有血有肉的人
because it made me feel almost like a person.
麦克斯 卡洛琳 你们好
Max, Caroline, hi.
我想感谢你们为我做的一切
I just wanted to say thank you for everything.
我刚看见你们俩一起跳舞
And I was watching you guys dance together,
现在我在想 或许我开始喜欢女人了
and now I'm thinking I might be into girls.
我可以打给你吗
Can I call you?
-可以 -不行
- Yes. - No.
太好了
Great.
你说什么 蛋糕下面写着无线电器材公司
What do you mean the bottom of the cake says Radio Shack?
我们该走了
That's our cue.
等等 我还没抛手捧花呢
Wait, wait, I haven't thrown the bouquet yet.
各位单身妹子
Hey, single ladies.
准备好了
Here we go.
一 二
One, two,
三
Three.
蛋糕妹
Hey, cake girls.
泡沫塑料
Styrofoam?
那个不含麸质哦
It's gluten-free.